<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<!-- Configurable parameters -->

<resources>

    <integer name="max_recipients">5</integer>
    <integer name="free_version_code">1</integer>
    <integer name="host_ads">0</integer>


    <string name="app_name">Bulk SMS</string>
    <integer name="versionCode">11</integer>
    <string name="versionName">@string/app_version</string>
    <string name="app_version">Version ( v2.2 ) 2017-02-10</string>

    <string name="version_history">
        "\n" "Version History :"
        "\n" "==============="
        "\n" "v1.0_2015-07-19 : Initial Bulk Sms App upload to GooglePlayStore."
        "\n" "v1.1_2015-07-28 : Minor UI changes incorporated."
        "\n" "v1.2_2015-07-29 : A Possible Bug isolated."
        "\n" "v1.3_2015-07-30 : Fixed freezing of List box in PhoneBook records.(Problem faced only on smaller screens). Added few more UI optimizations."
        "\n" "v1.4_2015-07-31 : Started working on "Reminder" part of the application."
        "\n" "v1.5_2015-08-01 : Set Reminder feature halfway. Releasing with few UI fixes."
        "\n" "v1.6_2015-08-04 : Promotional Email UI added. Spread a word with your friends. Select to send promotional emails to your friends."
        "\n" "v1.7_2015-08-05 : Code Beautification. (Nothing changed from end user perspective)."
        "\n" "v1.8_2015-08-05 : Code Beautification included a minor bug. Fixed."
        "\n" "v1.9_2015-08-06 : Bulk SMS Reminder finished. Releasing a test version."
        "\n" "v2.0_2015-08-08 : Version 2.0 Launched. Major UI change for better UX (User Experience). Bulk SMS Reminder available in free version too. Limit - 5 recipients max."
        "\n" "v2.1_2015-08-10 : Version 2.1 Launched. Major UI change for better UX (User Experience). Bulk SMS Reminder available in free version too. Limit - 5 recipients max. Added Contact Search for easy Phone Contacts selection"
        "\n" "v2.2_2017-02-10 : Version 2.2 Major UI change for better with cool UI animation effects."
    </string>

    <string name="app_about">
             "\n\n"
            "BULK SMS is aimed at users who wish to send one single message to huge number of recipients."
            "\n\n""How is it different from regular sms apps already available ? (You may ask). "
            "\n\n""Well, Bulk SMS v2.0 app provides you a feature where in you can set reminders (date,time) to send Birthday, Anniversary, Festive greetings to one or more recipients."
            "You have to set the Recipient, Message, Date &amp; Time, and leave rest to Bulk SMS app to take care of sending the message on appropriate Date and Time."
            "\n\n""Bulk SMS Reminder feature works even after you restart your phone."
            "\n\n""We would love to hear from you, your feedback, suggestions &amp; bugs(if any) to make Bulk SMS even better."
            "\n""e-mail: softwares.unleashed@gmail.com"
            "\n""Visit us @ www.softwaresunleashed.com"
            "\n\n""If you appreciate the work done by the developer of Bulk SMS app, please do take sometime out to rate this app on Google Store and Occasionally click on Ads. :)"

    </string>


    <string name="email_subject">New Android App -- Bulk SMS v2.2 (Complete UI revamp) -- Newly Launched!!!</string>
    <string name="email_body">
        "Dear Friend,"
        "\n\n" "Hope this mail finds you in great health!!"
        "\n""Your friend just used Bulk SMS to send messages to huge recipient list. We are sure you would like to give it a try as well."

        "\n\n""Allow us to introduce BULK SMS Android App. We have launched an exclusive app to send Bulk SMS to users. You are amongst first lucky few to have a preview of this useful app."
        "\n" "You can find it on Google Play too. You can install it from Google Play store. Search for 'Bulk SMS' on Google PlayStore "
        "\n\n""Here is the direct link to App, Bulk SMS, on Google Play Store."
        "\n\n""Link (Free - Limited Access) : https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.unleashed.android.bulksms1"
        "\n""Link (Paid - Full Access): https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.unleashed.android.bulksms2"
        "\n""Hope to hear from you!!"
        "\n""======================================"
        "\n""Software Unleashed Inc."
        "\n""url: www.softwaresunleashed.com"
        "\n""email: softwares.unleashed@gmail.com"
    </string>



    <!-- Banner Ad ID -->
    <string name="banner_ad_unit_id">ca-app-pub-9975842691888931/6757388200</string>

    <!-- Actual live banner for Bulk SMS...Use this in final production app
    <string name="banner_ad_unit_id">ca-app-pub-3940256099942544/6300978111</string>    - Test Ad ID
    <string name="banner_ad_unit_id">ca-app-pub-9975842691888931/6757388200</string>    - Live Ad ID
    -->

    <!-- Appszoom Ad : App Key-->
    <string name="az_appkey">bef9fbeddac73cb50854ebe6fdd0cbfc</string>

    <!-- Appszoom Ad : App Key-->
    <string name="adbuddiz_app_key">"9bd94a6a-6b11-4dd7-98b5-7b98522e78c8"</string>


</resources>
